Okay, regardless of which profile you
are on, you should now be able to get to
this repository page. Um, and now it'd
be nice to have more than just this
readme file here. It'd be nice to
actually put some code here. So, in
order to do that, we first have to get
this copy from the internet down onto
our computer. So, the way we do that is
we do something called cloning. Just
basically just copy the files from the
internet and put them on our computer.
So the way you do that is you'll open up
this code dropdown and then you're going
to click open with GitHub desktop. Now
the popup that pops up after this is
going to look slightly different on a
Windows versus a Mac. Um but the gist of
it is it's going to say open or cancel.
In our case, we're going to open with
GitHub Desktop and then it will open up
GitHub Desktop and it'll say okay out on
the internet there's a repository. It's
at that URL. Um, and then it'll say,
"Where do you want to put it on your
computer?" Well, right now it's asking
me if I want to put it in my 3D
tic-tac-toe folder. The answer is I do
not. So, what I'm going to do is I'm
going to go to my desktop. I'm going to
create a new folder. And I'm going to
call this demo repo.
And I'm going to select that and hit
select folder. So now I'm saying I want
to copy from the internet at that
location. And I want to copy it down
onto my computer at this location. And
then I'll hit clone.
And now it clones the repository.
And all right, it is now on our
computer. Just to prove it, I'm going to
click this open in Visual Studio Code
button.
What that does is it opens it up in
Visual Studio Code. We can see this
readme.md
and it says demo repo demonstrate
setting up a a code repository. And oh
boy,
if we look
at our repository online, it has that
exact same file. So if you um can click
open in Visual Studio Code and it opens
up and you can see that readme file that
we added, you have successfully cloned
the code to your own computer.